Osaka!
Not at all like Osaka!
Here we are!
Yay!
Laugh and eat your way to the top! Foodie championship!
Yeah!
What's the foodie championship?
We, Hamefurashi, are currently in Osaka!
Yes!
I meant that in a good way.
I'm sorry to bother you, but what do you think of Osaka?
Osaka means takoyaki, okonomiyaki, kushikatsu...
Kushikatsu.
That's a food-related thing, isn't it?
Yes, of course.
Pork buns.
It's all about food.
I'm a gourmand.
But, you know, Amefurashi is with Kyujinbo, so...
It's a perfect match, isn't it?
Does that mean we're going to eat our way through the day's food?
I skipped breakfast this morning.
So, I'm going to eat today!
I'll eat, I'll eat, I'll eat!
I'm going to eat breakfast.
Seriously...
Actually, Moeba is the one who wants to eat the most.
What are you talking about?
Send my dream through your line Send my dream through your line
My pretty fortune
I want to make it come true with you
On the green line
Tell me now
If it's just words, I don't need them anymore
It's up now, it's up now
You and me so unmanly
Laugh and eat your way to the top! It's the Eat and Laugh Battle Test
I can freely walk the streets of Osaka and eat what I want
What a surprise, from the office expenses these days!
Free food?
However, in honor of Osaka, the city of laughter
If you can make the staff laugh with a gag or an impromptu skit, that's OK!
But, gentlemen, there is hope.
No, I don't.
If you get a "gochi-nareru" square in the roulette, you get to eat unconditionally.
You have to treat the staff of Gokyunaru.
Eat your dinner!
We don't know the rules now, so you have to do it right.
Let's go again with the current cut.
Gentlemen, there is hope.
What? What is it?
When the roulette square that says "Eat, damn it!" comes up, you get to eat unconditionally.
I don't have to do anything?
You don't have to do anything.
One square?
Yes, one square.
But if the square that says "treat yourself" comes up, we have to buy the staff a meal.
But if we don't have to gag, it's fine. But, you know, if you don't have to gag me, well, that's good enough.
But on the other hand, please let me withdraw my money.
I haven't withdrawn any money yet.
This is a 300-yen necklace, right?
This is 1,400 yen!
Stop it! Don't upload it!
You idiot!
I understand. I'm planning to do it.
Pleased to meet you! Gag machine.
What's a machine?
Because everyone is laughing.
I'm sure I won't be able to eat a single piece today. They don't laugh at us.
To be honest, if we really stay at the Airieland machine, there is a big possibility that we won't be able to eat for the rest of our lives,
I really don't want to eat on my own.
It's a team competition this time.
But the manager of Amefura doesn't laugh too much.
Even when we are laughing, he never smiles and often looks at us as if he is wondering what we are doing.
They look at us coldly. That's not good.
Maybe it's partly because we usually do too much.
But this time we have Airira, who is going above and beyond,
Please do your best! Our mainstay!
Fighty!
Well then, everyone, let's do our best so that we can finish with a full stomach at the end!
I'll do my best!
I can do it!
Yeah! Ei! Ooh!
This is Bey.
Why are you changing?
What? Wasn't this the opening?
No, it wasn't.It wasn't.
It wasn't.
That's funny.
Why are you changing?
Take everyone's time.
It's what everyone says! Take time for Yuzu!
I'm going to eat until this happens!
Please, please, please.
Shall we go then!
Let's go!
I'm going!
Looks delicious! Someone has takoyaki!
Wait!
Can't you smell the crab?
So much crab!
I love crab doraku!
Crab fun!
Steak Work
I love crab doraku at Steakwork.
Is that bento?
Yes, yes, yes.
Crab man! Crab ice cream!
Crab man!
I want to eat crab.
I want crab.
I want to eat crab ice cream!
Crab Ice Cream
At first, I want to try my best to get crab ice cream and crab smear oyaki. At first I will try my best to go for crab ice cream and crab smear miyaki.
Yes, I will do my best. Let's do our best.
First of all, we will do the identity factory way, who will make you laugh.
This is important.
Because I could fly.
Start!
Oh no.
Oh, my God!
All of you!
It's disgusting.
Oh no.
Rather than pressure to do it alone, I think we should all warm up together.
Let's start with all of us.
That's a good idea.
Wait, this is the key.
If this is all of us or something, it's over.
Please.
One by one, one by one.
Ooh!
Two.
Well, well, well.
Four of us. I can't believe I made you two laugh.
Can you afford it?
Of course we can afford it.
Oh, no.
What do you want?
I want them to laugh.
No, thank you.
Okay, oh no, I'm hurt.
Oh, no. Oh, man.
Here we go!
Snow crab
Black Crab
Chestnut Crab
Crab masaa!
Wow!
Yay!
I laughed, even a little bit.
Great, cool.
That's not cool.
I mean, that ping pong would've gone so far.
Look at that.
You laughed.
But you really laughed.
But you laughed.
Yay!
Yay! - Yay!
I can't do it anymore.
Ready, go!
Snow crab.
Black crab
Crab.
Gani Masa
by H.
Bon appétit!
Delicious!
Very tasty!
Delicious!Delicious.
It's so soft and juicy.
Delicious.
Flesh is packed tightly.
The meat is delicious.
I used to eat only crab cakes.
Don't say "kanikama.
It's not crab.
Next, crab ice cream!
Delicious!
Yum! Yum! Yum!
It has a nice sweet and sour taste.
But totally easy to eat!
Yum!
I ate it for a year.
Delicious!
It's so good!
It's really good.
Bon appétit!
I'm hungry.
I'm not hungry at all!
I want to go home! I really want to go home!
I really want to go home!